哈里.胡迪尼(逃脱艺术家)/于1911年发明了中国式水牢
Chinese water torture cell was/invented in 1911 by harry houdini.
没有新材料
Nothing like new material.
他头朝下入水
He was lowered head/first into the water.
脚踝上锁固定在水箱顶部
His ankles were locked and/bolted to the top of the tank.
我需要一位志愿者
I'm gonna need a volunteer.
手快脱臼的那位男士...
The guy dislocating his shoulder...
可以叫你隔壁的男士上来吗?
could you tell the guy/next to you to come up?
快上去 去啊 快点!
Come on,get up there,man.Get/up there,get up there!Come on!
快点儿!
Come on!
- 我们之前见过吗?/- 没有
- Hi.Have we met before?/- No.
要是你答是 就可以回去坐了
See,if you said yes,you could/have gone back to your seat.
你可以向观众保证这缸水是真的吗?
Now,can you vouch for this audience/that this is a glass tank f water?
- 可以/- 不 你还不可以
- Yeah./- No,you can'T.
你还没有测试 过来
You haven't done anything yet.Come on.
敲敲玻璃缸
Knock on the glass.
坚实的玻璃 敲一下
Solid glass.Knock on it.
水也是真的
It's real water too.
Ilana给他泼点水
Ilana,splash the guy.
- 感觉到湿吗?/- 是的
- Does that feel wet to you?/- Yeah.
你认为这就代表是水了?
And you think that proves it's water?
我想我们见过
I think we have met.
你去过奥马哈东部
Do you know the public washroom behind
- 车站后的公共卫生间吗?/- 不
- the truck stop east of omaha?/- No.
要是你答是 就有趣多了
See,if you'd said yes,that/would have been so funny.
把手伸出来给我
Hold out your arms for me.
- 以前这么干过?/- 没有
- You've done this before,right?/- No.
两者选其一 你又选了无趣的那个
Again,two choices,and you/went for the unfunny one.
记住
Now,remember,
你们只能做一件事...
there's only one thing/you've got to be able to do...
把喊叫着绑着锁链的男人拉出水箱
drag a screaming,crying,shackled/man out of a tank of water.
升!
Up!
你会游泳吧?
Hey,you can swim,right?
哇喔 说你会游泳
Whoa,whoa,tell me you can swim.
我会
Yeah.
两者选其一啊
Two answers,man.
就两个答案!
Two answers!
这也是演出来的吗?
Is that part of the act?
我是新来的 我想是吧
I'm new.I think so.
大概不是
Maybe not.
快上来!
Get up here!
五个饥渴医生 一个病人没有
five eager doctors,and no sick people.
我们来点新挑战解闷吧
Let us try and fill our spare/time with a new challenge.
- 胜者有免死金牌.../- 我有病人
- The winner gets an immunity/- I have a sick guy.
- 我昨晚见到一个魔术师.../- 女孩不会有事的
- I saw this magician last night.../- the girl's fine.
他没真的把她锯成两半
He didn't really cut her inalf.
他倒悬在水箱时心跳停止了
His heart stopped while he was/hanging upside down in the water tank.
溺水者心脏停止 好神秘啊
Drowning man's heart/stopped.That is a mystery.
除了免死金牌 胜者还有权提名两...
Along with immunity,the/winner gets to nominate two...
他刚接触到水就失去知觉了
he lost consciousness almost/as soon as he hit the water.
晚上6点才能下班
You have to leave work at 6:00 P.M.,
还有兴致结伴去找乐子?
But you make time for man dates?
- 是什么样的挑战?/- 我们不可以做朋友吗?
- What's the challenge?/- Are we not allowed to be friends?
不 我只是有点受伤
No,I'm just hurt.
- 我叫你陪我去看妈妈咪呀(歌剧).../- 无心脏病史 无心绞痛
- When I asked you to come see mama mia.../- no history of heart disease.No angina.
- 无.../- 他说谎了
- No.../- he's lying.
病史上说谎? 急诊室确定...
About his history? E.R. confirmed
每件事都说谎 他是个魔术师/以此为生的
About everything.He's a/magician.That's what they do.
搞砸了戏法 溺水了 心搏就停止了
He screwed up the trick,he started/drowning,he got a cardiac arrest.
你刚才说的挑战?
You were talking about a challenge?
胜者可提名...
The winner nominates...
两个竞争对手
two of your competitors.
我会炒其中一个
I will fire one of them.
即使他是溺水了
Even if he was drowning,
也不会这么快引发心脏病
it would have taken longer/to set off a cardiac incident
- 没有潜在问题的话.../- 好了
- without some underlying problem that.../- fine.
你想测就测吧
Go run your tests.
- 要是你错了 就炒你/- 要是我对了 就能留下?
- If you're wrong,you're fired./- If I'm right,do I stay?
要是我说不是 难道你要见死不救?
If I say no,are you gonna/let your patient die?
什么挑战?
What's the challenge?
我们为打破常规的医生喝彩
We can all applaud the doctor who's/willing to break all the rules.
但真英雄是那些无人歌颂的医生
But the real hero is the unsung doctor,
无名英雄
toiling in anonymity,
因为他打破常规又不露痕迹
'cause he broke the rules/without getting caught.
我想知道你们是否有这现能力
I need to know you have these skills.
我要你们...
I need you...
把Lisa Cuddy的内裤给我拿来
to bring me the thong of lisa cuddy.
不是玩笑
Not kidding.
内裤 Cuddy 开始
Thong.Cuddy.Go.
我也是这么受雇的
It's how I got hired.
你真要做?
you're actually considering this?
你要想坚守原则
If you want to stand on principle,
我很尊重你
I really respect you for that.
这是孩子气 不专业 不恰当的
It's childish,unprofessional,
不值得为工作这么做
and inappropriate, the job is not worth it.
我们该口径一致
We should all beg off.
告诉他我们失败了
Tell him we failed.
无胜者 无输家
No winners,no losers.
好
Fine.
你还是会去做的 对吧?
You're gonna do it,aren't you?
我当然会
Of course i'm gonna do it.
无瓣膜反流
no valvular regurgitation,
无室壁运动异常 无结构缺陷
no wall motionabnormalities,/no structural defects.
要不是你语调沮丧 我以为是好消息呢
If you didn't sound so/despondent,I'd say that was good news.
对你是好消息 对他不是
It is for you,not for him.
最近有没有觉得腿部沉重?
Notice any heaviness in your/legs the last couple days?
为什么对你不是好消息?
Why isn't it good news for you?
因为你要是没事 他就被解雇了
Because,if there's nothing/wrong with you,he gets fired.
- 真的?/- 有点认真 你腿怎样?
- Seriously?/- Somewhat seriously.Your legs?
不觉得有异常
Haven't noticed anything/out of the ordinary.
- 呼吸短促?/- 要是我吐了 能帮到你吗?
- Shortness of breath?/- Would it help if I puked?
选张牌
Pick a card.
胸部和手臂有紧绷感吗?
Any tightness in your chest or arms?
- 选张牌/- 你不是很担心啊
- Pick a card./- You don't seem too worried.
可以请你选张牌吗?
Would you please pick a card?
我们老大认为你的心博停止是
Our boss thinks your cardiac arrest was
意外溺水的结果
just a result of you/accidentally drowning.
你们老大是白痴 放回去
Your boss is an idiot.Put it back.
洗牌
Shuffle 'em up.
那你为什么不担心?
So then why aren't you worried?
要么死掉要么活着
Either I'm dying or I'm not.
我不想死
I mean,I don't want the ride to be over,
可忧心忡忡也治不了病...
but unless worrying is/some new form treatment...
- 你的牌/- 不是
- yo card./- No.
要为食管超声心动图作准备了
I'm goa prep you foa/transesophageal echo.
你确认洗过牌?
You sure you shuffled these?
要给你打镇静剂
And I'm gonna need to sedate you.
先检查一下你的钱包吧
Might wanna check your wallet first.
可以看看钱包吗? 这是魔术的一部份
Would you check your/wallet?It's part of the trick.
噢
Oh.
那是我的牌 怎么做到的?
That's my card.How did you do that?
再来一次
Do it again.
- 以为你放弃了/- 没有
- thought you weren't playing./- I'm not.
要是你被抓到 她会解雇你的
She'll fire you if she catches you.
我没打算偷她内裤 她怎么解雇我
Don't think she can fire me for/not trying to steal her panties.
你打算用意念让裤裤掉下来?
You trying to will them off?
我要是有计划
If I had a plan,
第一步就是不告诉你计划是怎样的
the first part would be not/telling you what the plan was.
- 你还没喝过这杯咖啡呢/- 我喝过了
- You haven't touched that coffee./- Yes,I have.
如果裤裤湿了 她就得脱下
She can't keep her/panties on if they're wet.
我们合伙
We work together.
赢的那个保护另一个
One wins,protects the other.
或者我独赢
Or I win by myself,
然后你央求我不要点你的名
and then you try desperately/to convince me to spare you.
Cuddy医生
dr.Cuddy.
Taub医生 你还好吧?
Dr.Taub,are you okay?
只是绊了一跤 抱歉
I...I just tripped.I'm so sorry.
我有空 门诊需要人手吗?
I have some extra time.Do you/need any help in the clinic?
好
okay.
没发现什么能引起停博的
we found no apparent/cause for the arrest.
经胸超声和食道超声心动图都没显示出...
T.T.E.And T.E.E.Revealed no...
让病人回家吧 你还可以顺道载他
send the patient home.You/can give him a lift.
我们查了凝块 查了...
We checked for clots.We checked for...
你向我汇报是因为你害怕向House汇报
you're reporting to me because/you're scared to report to House
你什么都查不到 这不是个奇特的病例
because you found/nothing,because this isn't a case.
- 你以为我可以帮你/- 是的
- And you thought i'd save your ass./- Yeah.
我认为他有病 我该怎么做去证实?
I thought he was sick.What/was i supposed to do?
他的肺有事吗?
What about his lungs?
含氧饱和度降低导致心脏病发
Decreased oxygen saturation/leads to heart failu
急诊室没查出什么
E.R.Dn't find anything.
急诊室没查 忙着救活他呢
E.R.Wasn't looking.Too busy/trying to keep him alive.
去做核磁共振吧
Get an mri.
请叫Cuddy医生来护士站 尽快
Yes,can you ask dr.Cuddy to/come to the nurse's station,stat?
我让你叫Cuddy医生...
I asked you to get doctor...
Taub医生说她马上出来
dr.Taub said she'd be right out.
肺部有真菌?
A fungus in my lungs?
我怎么会得那种东西?
How would I even get/something like that?
现在只是个理论
Right now,it's just a theory.
我们不知道是不是...
We don't even know if it's...
就知道大学时不该磕迷幻蘑菇
I knew I shouldn't have done/those mushrooms in college.
那肯定与此无关
I'm sure there's no connection.
开玩笑的
It was a joke.
工作危在旦夕时 你连幽默感都没了啊?
You really lose your sense of humor/when your job's on the line,huh?
抱歉 大部分快死的人都不会...
Sorry.Most dying people/don't really like to...
不是说你快死
not that you're dying.
- 但稍微有点小病就对了吧?/- 对
- But a little sick would be perfect,right?/- Yeah.
我的肚子!
My stomach!
刺痛还是抽痛?
Stabbing or throbbing?
腹膜后出血的症状 他内出血
Grey turner's sign.He's/got internal bleeding
我去叫外科医生
I'll call surgeons
外科输了3单位的AB型血
surgeons  have transfused/three units ab positive,
但出血源还没找到
but they're still looking/for the source of the bleed.
无外伤 可能是肝病 维他命K缺乏症
No trauma.Could be liver/disease.Vitamin k deficiency.
唯一可排除的...
The only thing we know/for sure it's not...
就是他没病的论断
nothing.
肝病一类的慢性病 我们早该发觉
and we would have noticed something/chronic like liver disease.
很可能肠道梗死...
It's probably an intestinal infarct...
我来!
I got it!
Cuddy的底裤
Eau de cuddy.
不可能
no way.
- 你怎么得手的?/- 只有一个办法
- How did you get them?/- Only one way.
这不是Cuddy的内裤
These are not cuddy's panties.
- 你认为我没.../- 对
- You don't think that I.../- no.
她今天戴红色的胸罩
Also,she's wearing a red bra today.
不是只有我一个人注意到
Like I'm the only one who noticed.
内裤肯定配成一套
Means the downstairs will match.
做好调查 筒子
Do your research,people.
肠道梗死可能导致心搏停止
An intestinal infarct could be/linked to the cardiac arrest.
- 撩起裙子/- 太粗鲁了 就算是你
- Hike up your skirt./- Wow,that's rude,even for you.
往下撩也行
Hike it down then.
你戴的是黑色的胸罩
You're wearing a black bra.
- 让我们看看你的内裤/- 不!
- Let's see the underwear./- No!
你们两个合伙了
You two cut a deal.
不作弊就不算尽力
If you're not cheating,you're/not trying hard enough.
那她是不是没穿内裤?
Is she not wearing any underwear?
这有个人正出血呢...
um,there's a guy bleeding...
Foreman 她没穿内裤呢
foreman,she's not wearing any underwear.
你以前可没这么无趣
You used to be more fun.
她没穿内裤呢...很了不起
She's not wearing any/underwear...big deal.
等她啥都不穿了
When she stops wearing clothes,
我们就不谈医务吧
then we can drop the medical stuff.
- 把磁共振图给我看/- 没图呢
- Let me see the mri film./- Oh,we didn't get any images.
我一开机他就开始尖叫了
He started screaming as/soon as I turned it on.
有多快?
Define "soon."
我还没来得及坐下
I didn't even get a chance to sit down.
你们想过
You guys ever wonder
他怎么能从水箱里出来?
how he was gonna get/out of that water tank?
你...跟来
You...come.
消化道缺口
Lacerations in his digestive tract.
他的脾碎了
And his spleen is shredded.
女士先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我手中无物 袖里没机关
I have nothing in my/hands,nothing up my sleeve.
裤子里倒是有料
I do have something in my pants,
但对这个戏法却没有帮助
but it's not gonna help/with this particular trick.
认真看啦
Watch closely.
- 最近可好?/- 在此前都还好
- How ya been?/- Fine.Till now.
嗒-哒!
Ta-da!
如此...
Now you...
逃脱困笼
disappear.
眼熟吗?
look familiar?
磁共振的强磁把它从肠道拽到脾里
The mri's magnet ripped this through/your intestine into your spleen.
忘了这东西
Forgot about that.
差点死掉嘛
On account of almost dying.
Kutner在哪?
Where's dr.Kutner?
他不再跟你的病例了
He's no longer on your case.
因为你没病
'Cause there's nothing wrong with you.
我并没有搞砸那次魔术
I didn't screw up that trick.
所有这些
Everything that's happened
都可以归咎于你的健忘和不称职
can be explained by you being/forgetful and incompetent.
你搞砸了 昏过去了...
You screwed up,you passed out...
知道我最喜欢什么时候说谎吗?
know my favorite time to lie?
当我命悬一线的时候
When my life hangs in the balance.
你没有命悬一线
Your life doesn't hang in the balance.
你知道你没有命悬一线
You know your life doesn't/hang in the balance.
你的声誉倒是悬了...
Your reputation might hang...
小时候喜欢魔术吗?
you ever do magic as a kid?
你像那种... 孤独 执迷的
You seem like the/type... lonely,obsessive.
我长大了 你呢?
I outgrew it.You?
点一张牌
Pick a card.
太麻烦了
Too much trouble.
- 我挖挖鼻孔成吗?/- 我不是三流角色
- Can I just pick my nose?/- I'm not a hack.
如果我猜出你接下来怎么做/你能老实回家吗?
If I tell you how it's/done,will you go home?
你要使它神奇地出现在我的钱包里?
So you gonna make it/magically appear in my wallet?
你真是三流的
You are a hack.
我不会搞砸的
I don't screw up.
流那么多鼻血意味着他有病
A nosebleed that major/means he's actually sick.
意味着心搏停止是个症状
Means the cardiac arrest was a symptom.
别翘尾巴
Stop gloating.
- 我没得意/- 那为什么奸笑?
- I'm not gloating./- Then what's that smirk?
哪有 长得就这样
No smirk.This is how I look.
那个内衣贼大考验怎么办?
what about the underwear challenge?
我正式宣布比赛暂停
I declare it officially on hold.
不算很光彩 但我搞到手了
Not really fair,but I get it.
确实是Cuddy的
It's cuddy'S.
把你的裤子脱了
Pull down your pants.
- 你觉得我在诳你/- 不是
- You think I'm lying?/- No.
我要好好奖励你
I wanna give you a reward.
是 我觉得你在诳我
Yes,I think you're lying.
心跳停止加上鼻出血...开始
Cardiac arrest plus nose bleed...go.
没有显著相关家族病史
Uh,patient has no/significant family history,
无心绞痛 先前无发作记录
no angina,no prior attacks.
如果问题不在心脏
what if it isn't his heart?
而在心脏周围的血管呢?
What if it's the/vessels around his heart?
结节性多动脉炎会引起心脏病症状
Polyarteritis nodosa/causes cardiac symptoms
以及高血压 导致鼻出血
and hypertension,which/makes his nose bleed.
知道还有什么会让你流鼻血 心脏狂跳?
you know what else makes your/nose bleed and your heart race?
可卡因
Cocaine.
这家伙在大西洋城二流的夜总会表演
Guy works in a b-list/nightclub in atlantic city.
肯定经常性吸食可卡因
He's gotta be taking/regular rolls in the snow.
你带这自鸣得意的家伙去病人的毒巢
You,take the gloater to/the patient's drug den.
别忘了 离开前搜一下他的口袋
Make sure you pat down his/pockets before you leave.
你和博爱 活检心脏周围的血管
You and big love,biopsy of blood/vessel from around the heart.
查结节性多动脉炎
Test for polyarteritis nodosa.
你嘛...
You...
到我办公室来
in my office.
那不是我的
Those aren't my panties.
我知道
I know.
假设
Hypothetical.
一位姑娘在众人面前笨手笨脚
A young woman does/something clumsy in public.
她没有一笑了之 而是情绪低落
And instead of laughing it/off,she gets irrationally upset.
为什么?
Explain.
她大概是紧张了 才会笨手笨脚
Maybe she's clumsy 'cause she's nervous,
可能她忘记了做拼写功课
'cause she forgot to do/her spelling homework.
我猜测 她八岁
In my hypothetical,she's eight.
但这姑娘不缺乏自信
But this girl's not insecure.
更像是害怕什么?
Seems more like she's afraid.
你到底想说什么/刚买了本脑筋急转弯的书?
Do you have a point,or did you/just get a new book of riddles?
我觉得你对健康状况有所隐瞒
I think you're hiding/a medical condition.
没有
I'm not.
很高兴能和你谈话
I'm glad we had this talk.
医者都觉得自己百病不侵
Doctors often try to
所以常常无视自己身上的病症
ignore their symptoms 'cause/they think they can't get sick.
如果你生了病 你得医治
If you got something going on,I/need you to take care of it.
- 我相信你是真心同情我/-不是同情
- And I take your compassion entirely at face value./- It's not compassion.
我维护自身利益 我要一个健康的团队
It's self-interest.I/want my team healthy.
这不是维护自身利益 是好奇
It's not self-interest.It's curiosity.
House 要是我拿不住文件
I dropped a file,House.
眼睛出血
I start bleeding from the eyes,
我保证会预约去看医生
I'll be sure to make an appointment.
好吧
Okay.
- 啊 有大麻/- 打包带走
- eh,found some pot./- bag it.
我不认为大麻和病患的症状相符
I'm not sure it really/fits the symptoms.
当然不相符 但把它落在这太不负责了
Of course not,but it'd be/irresponsible to leave it here.
- 有硬币么/- 没有
- You have a quarter?/- No.
Cole是怎么把Cuddy的裤裤扒下来的?
How did cole get those/panties off cuddy?
肯定不是她穿的 不可能是她的
They were never on/her.No way those are hers.
兔热病
Tularemia.
不可能 那得先有兔子啊
No,you'd have to have rabbits.
对...兴许是虱子从兔子身上跃下
True...maybe a tick/jumped from a rabbit and
跳到其中一只毛茸茸的白鳄鱼上
landed on one of these/white,fluffy alligators.
再然后跳到了病人身上
Then it jumps onto our patient,
传播了细菌 引起心包炎
transfers the/bacteria,causes pericarditis.
可以解释所有症状
Explains everything.
你要给我用什么药?
What are you giving me?
你的把戏是怎么耍的?
How'd you do the trick?
哦 说破就平凡无奇了
Oh,if I explain,it becomes mundane,
真实的魔力会消失
and you lose the actual magic.
真实的魔力是什么?
What do you mean,the actual magic?
真以为自己把女郎锯成两段
Think you're actually/sawing women in half?
你到底告不告诉我是什么病?
You gonna tell me what's/wrong with me or not?
魔力很酷
Magic is cool.
真实的魔力却有些自相矛盾
Actual magic is oxymoronic.
没那么奇妙
Might not even be oxy.
我不告诉你 你就不告诉我?
You're not gonna tell/me unless I tell you?
你让护士帮你把牌放好的
You got a nurse to plant the card.
护士甚至不肯帮我尿尿
I can't get a nurse to help me pee.
你让你朋友帮你摆牌
You got a buddy to plant the card.
乐在
The fun...
不知其所以然
is in not knowing.
乐在...
The fun...
知其所以然
is in knowing.
哦 我的头
Oh,my head.Oh!
我的头好痛
I got a headache.
多痛? 第一次出现?
How bad?Is it new?
不算太痛 我只要吃一片...
It's not too bad.I'll...I'll/just take one of these...
维柯丁就好了
vicodin.
你吃太多甜菜根
You eat a lot of beets,
用的是电动牙刷
you have an electric toothbrush,
每天睡不超过6个小时
and you sleep less/than six hours a night.
很厉害啊
That's impressive.
红色的甜菜碱使牙菌斑着色
The red betamine from the beets stains/the plaque deposits on your teeth,
被电动牙刷转成漩涡状
which are then swirled by/your spinning toothbrush.
而你抬不起眼皮 皮肤未老先衰
Your heavy lids and your/prematurely aging skin
都告诉我你需要好好补觉了
tell me that you're/carrying a major sleep debt.
你不解释的话 听起来拉风多了
That was way cooler/before you explained it.
解释了才会有意义
It was meaningless until I explained it.
来看我表演的人想要感受奇迹
People come to my show because/they want a sense of wonder.
想要体验茫茫未知
They want to experience/something that they can't explain.
如果真相显现 奇迹就褪去了
If the wonder's gone/when the truth is known,
那说明从未有过什么奇迹
there never was any wonder.
你从兔子那里感染了兔热病
You have tularemia from your rabbits.
我已经给你挂了抗生素 你几天后就会康复了
I've put you on antibiotics.You'll/be better in a couple of days.
抱歉打破了你的神秘感
Sorry to spoil the mystery.
谢谢
Thank you.
这个很重要 一定要做好
Because it's very important/to actually do it well.
我来捡吧
I'll get it.
Oh...
我的
my...
老天!
god!
你裙子里是真空的
You're not wearing underwear!
- 当然不是 我.../- 裙子那么紧 一览无遗
- Of course,I'm.../- skirt that tight,you got no secrets.
紧得可以看出有没有用宫内避孕器
Skirt that tight,I can/tell if you got an I.U.D.
你和Cole医生约会?
You've seen dr.Cole?
没有
No.
- 脸红了/- 没有
- You're blushing./- I am not.
看着我
Look at me.
Oh...
我的
my...
天!
god!
怎么做到的?
How'd you do it?
这么说我豁免了?
So I'm safe?
你说这份工? 是的
In this job,yeah.
但是 你的老二处境堪忧...
Crotch,on the other hand...
怎么做到的?
how'd you do it?
主要靠祈祷
Prayer,mostly.
就告诉我
Just tell me.
Cuddy惹火吗?
Does cuddy have her groove back?
讨论这个太不礼貌了
It'd be rude of me to discuss.
你把她的内裤偷来给我
You handed over her panties.
现在还想向她献殷勤 为时太晚了
I don't think gallantry's/really an option at this point.
如果我告诉你 就不神奇了
If I tell you,then where's the magic?
他昏过去了
he passed out.
超声波扫描显示心脏附近出血
Ultrasound revealed/bleeding around his heart.
吸出了100毫升才止住
We drained 100 ccs before it stopped.
抗生素没有效果
The antibiotics aren't working.
很明显不是兔热病或其他感染
It's obviously not tularemia/or any other infection.
不好意思...我们还没说完
Excuse me... we were talking.
心脏附近出血说明活检结果可能有错
bleeding around the heart/could mean botched biopsy
那时候Cole正忙着...
when cole was looking for the...
你的前途掌握在他手中/你怎么能指控他搞砸了?
why would you accuse the man who/decides your fate of screwing up?
那真的是Cuddy的?
those really were her panties?
Cole披荆斩棘
Cole has traveled through/the forest of crustaceans
把珍宝带给大家
and brought us a treasure.
他应得到奖励
And he has earned his reward.
- 我只要得到免死金牌就够了/- 不行 Sophie 你还是得选人
- If I could just get the immunity,I.../- no,sophie,you can'T.
用什么标准随便你
Use whatever criteria you want.
可能是血栓
Could be a clotting issue.
如果他有弥漫性血管内凝血
if he developed D.I.C.
术后正常活检都会导致大失血
After the surgery,even a normal/biopsy bleeds out of control.
心脏停跳 弥漫性血管内凝血
So cardiac arrest and D.I.C.
- 有什么共通之处?/- 可能是癌症
- What's the common denominator?/- Could be cancer.
他入院后一直在查胸腔 不是癌症
We've been looking in his chest/since he got here...it's clean.
那么大肿块在别的地方
so the main mass is somewhere else...
产生血栓 堵塞心脏动脉 造成心脏停跳
throws up a clot,blocks an artery/in his heart,causes the arrest.
很好!
Good!
去查他把肿瘤藏在什么地方
Go find out where/he's hiding his cancer.
如果你还吞过别的金属
if you swallowed any more metal,
现在说还不迟
now would be a good time to tell us.
我的手有点麻
My hands feel kind of numb.
你失血过多
You lost a lot of blood.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
每个人在医院里都会感到害怕
Everybody gets scared in a hospital.
- 你是病了 所以感觉糟糕/- 不是
- You're sick,you feel awful.../- no.
明日此时
This time tomorrow.
是我的死期
I'll be dead.
谁会被点名?
So who's going on the block?
他觉得他快死了
He thinks he's dying.
也许他说得没错
He's probably right.
死于明天
Tomorrow.
如果你选我 我非常理解
You decide to put me/up,I totally get it.
我对事不对人
Nothing personal.
我还没有决定
I haven't decided anything.
但你不喜欢我
But you don't like me.
我喜欢你
I like you.
肺内积水
Some fluid in the lungs.
没有肿块
No masses.
我玩阴的
I'm manipulative.
不守规矩
I play the game.
不在乎做个贱人
I can be a bitch.
有暗斑
There's a dark spot.
钥匙撕裂造成的损伤
Damage from where the/key ripped through.
你可能以为我会诋毁别人
You're probably expecting/me to bash the others,
列举他们败事有余的例子
give examples of how they screwed up.
我会的
You know I can.
我是个好医生
I'm a good doctor.
和医院里的其他人一样优秀
As good as anybody around here.
也许更优秀
Probably better.
这才是关键
You know that's the/only thing that matters.
这是什么?
what's that?
不是肿瘤 是另一处出血
It's not a tumor. It's another bleed.
在肾脏
This one's in his kidney.
还有大腿股
And his thigh.
这块区域都在出血
He's bleeding all over the place.
他的大限 他也许说对了
His timetable may be right on.
很诡异
it was creepy.
病人预言了自己的死亡
The patient predicted his own death.
如果他预言自己不会死的话 就更牛了
would have been more impressive if/he'd predicted that he wasn't gonna die.
当然 要多费些时间才能证明
Of course,that takes longer to prove.
可以看成是一种症状
could be a symptom.
感觉末日即将降临
Sense of impending doom.
可能是肾上腺紊乱 出血 过敏反应
Yeah,could be adrenal gland/disorders,blood issues,anaphylaxis.
如果你要拍他马屁来自保
If you're gonna kiss his/ass to protect your ass,
起码也等他有个好点的想法
at least wait until/he's had a good idea.
他假充高人是一种病症
It's a symptom of him being a charlatan.
他是二流的魔术师 一级古怪的病
He's a second-rate magician/with a mysterious illness.
他不预言自己的死期可就亏了
Why wouldn't he predict his own death?
错了 没人记得
If he's wrong,we all forget it.
对了 就成了传奇
If he's right,he goes out a legend.
他在输血后就变得恐惧
he got scared right after a transfusion.
血液感染会诱发病人担忧厄运
Tainted blood has been known to/cause a sense of impending doom.
也可以解释弥漫性血管内凝血
Could also explain the D.I.C.
我预言你们的呼机齐鸣... 就现在
I predict all your/pagers go off...right now.
如果真响了...
But if it had happened...
有人看过他的血检指标么?
anyone bother looking at his panel?
免疫球蛋白偏低
His immunoglobulin levels are low.
不能明确说明...
That doesn't tell us/anything specific about...
因为不会被淘汰 你就卖傻么 ?
are you acting stupid/'cause you know you're safe?
好聪明
Clever.
低免疫球蛋白 心脏衰竭 肺部积水 内出血
low immunoglobulin plus failing heart,plus/fluid in the lungs,plus internal bleeding,
等于淀粉样变性病
equals amyloidosis.
淀粉样变性病不会出这么多血
He's bleeding way too/much for amyloidosis.
他有没有感觉手脚无力?
Say anything about his/hands or feet feeling weak?
他说手麻木 但失血过多可以解释
he said his hands felt numb,but/that's explained by the blood loss.
不要
No!
千万别夸我未卜先知
Do not give me credit for that.
毫厘之差就不能算
Close doesn't count.
人就是这么变愚钝的
That's how people get/sucked into this stupidity.
他痉挛发作了
He's seizing.
谁去稳定病情
Somebody stabilize him.
剩下的 去查医疗记录
Rest of you,pull his medical records.
从十年前查起
Go back ten years.
关节痛 疲劳 任何和淀粉样变性病有关的
Look for joint pain,fatigue,anything/associated with amyloidosis.
Finn 听得到请点头
Mr.Finn, nod if you can hear me.
你僵直阵挛发作
you had a grand mal seizure.
现在给你输液 用抗惊厥药
We're giving you liquids/and an anticonvulsant.
请尽量安定下来
Just try to rest.
脉搏趋缓 情况稳定了
Pulse is dropping. He's stabilizing.
你不会挑我吧?
You're not gonna put/me on the block,are you?
我还没决定
I haven't decided who I'm gonna pick.
好吧
That's cool.
你觉得他脚浮肿么?
His legs look swollen to you?
轻微浮肿可能与肾脏有关
Slight swelling could be renal.
我帮你带孩子
I babysat for you.
我决定让称职的人留下
I decided I'm gonna make my decision/based solely on who deserves to be here.
值得尊敬 虽然很傻
That's admirable,though stupid.
你不应该留下最牛的
You shouldn't save the strongest.
应该踢掉最牛的
You should get rid of the strongest.
消灭能和你竞争的人 那肯定不是我
Eliminate your competition,which/is definitely not me.
我和你可是朋友
And I'm your friend.
再说 难道你打算告诉孩子
And how are you gonna/explain to your kid
你把我给炒了 所以下周没人带他去动物园?
that I can't take him to the zoo/next week because you got me fired?
Kutner
Kutner.
他又痉挛了
He's gonna seize again.
腰肋部疼痛 肾脏开始衰竭
Flank pain. His kidneys/are shutting down.
更甚...
Also...
Amber是种族主义者
amber's a racist.
你知道他们的呼机会响?
you knew they'd get paged?
我注意到一个趋势...
I noticed a trend...
当大家都不干活的时候/病人的病情会加重
if nobody does anything,sick/people often get sicker.
你认为他们发生关系了吗?
You think it's remotely/possible they had sex?
他们都还是单身
They're both single.
在民主党当权的州 这是合法的
It's still legal in the blue states.
她几乎不认识他
She barely knows him.
在某些国度
You know,in some cultures,
雇人偷取他人内衣 是求爱的表现
hiring people to steal someone's/underpants is considered wooing.
你应该搬去那住
You should move there.
在这 你只会让人心里发毛
Because here it's just,you know,creepy.
没求爱什么事
There was no woo.
这是个很有效的测试
This was an effective test.
恕我无法理解
This is beneath my skills.
肾衰竭
kidneys are shutting down.
导致钠缺乏
Led to a sodium deficiency.
引起痉挛
Caused him to seize.
肾衰竭说明是淀粉样变病
Kidney failure means I was/right about amyloidosis.
但病历上没有任何与之相关的记录
Except that nothing in his medical/history remotely indicates amyloidosis.
肾衰竭表示是血液污染 我说对了
So kidney failure proves i'm/right about the bad blood.
血液污染无法解释心脏和肝脏的问题
Bad blood doesn't explain/the heart or the liver.
他的主要症状都是输血之后再出现的
His major symptoms didn't start/until after we transfused him.
心脏停跳不算主要症状了吗?
Is cardiac arrest no longer/considered a major symptom?
溺水导致的话就不算
Not when it's caused by drowning.
所以说 你接下这个病例是因为你白痴?
So your new theory is that/you're an idiot to take this case.
对 我可以去验证一下吗?
Yes. Can I go test that theory now?
浪费时间
Waste of time.
是淀粉样变性 他需要骨髓移植
He needs a bone marrow/transplant for the amyloidosis.
移植前要放射治疗
You'd have to irradiate him first.
如果真是血液问题
If they're right about the blood,
等于白白摧毁了他的免疫系统
you'd be destroying his/immune system for nothing.
倒也不见得是坏事
Which could be a good thing.
他活得很失败吗?
Does he have a really crappy life?
有本事尽管去查
Go prove I'm right.
做皮下脂肪活检
Do a subcutaneous fat biopsy.
至少让我们排除血液污染的可能性
At least let us eliminate/the bad blood theory,
去血库查有没有被污染和标记错误
check the blood banks for/mis-marks and contamination.
给你们两个小时
You've got two hours.
你太草率了
That's completely arbitrary.
不 我要给你们三个阴历月
No,if I'd said that you/got three lunar months,
那才叫草率
that'd be completely arbitrary.
两个小时是让博爱完成活检的时间
Two hours is how long it's gonna take big/love to finish a biopsy that you guys can't do
你们不肯做活检 非要查血液
because you're wasting/two hours checking blood.
9比3
9-3.
5盘定胜负
5-all.
嘿 从餐厅给你带了些吃的
Hey. Brought you something/from the cafeteria.
不是行贿
It's not a bribe.
这才是贿赂
This is a bribe.
多少?
How much?
一百万
$1 million.
五千啦
$5,000.
这太离谱了
This is so wrong.
House特别说明了 你可以根据任何标准选择
House specifically said you can/use whatever criteria you want.
我有钱
I've got money.
你需要钱
You need money.
切片给我
Hand me that slide.
你的薪水和我一样 少得可怜
Right now,you're earning what/I'm earning,which is miserable.
我知道你的孩子读哪所学校
I know what school your kid's at.
我知道那得花多少钱
I know what it costs.
我见过他的照片
I've seen his picture.
他该戴牙套了
He's gonna need braces.
红细胞正常
no R.B.C. Damage.
血库没有异常
nothing wrong with storage.
我再对比一下血型 做血液培养
I'm gonna double-check/type and start cultures.
我们还剩32分钟
we've still got 32 minutes left.
时光飞逝啊
Time flies.
有结果吗
What have you found?
你过来查岗...
You're checking up on them...
看来Cole做完活检了 结果是否定的
that means cole's finished with/the biopsy,and it was negative.
是不确定
Inconclusive.
脂肪不能说明什么
Fat doesn't always give you the answer.
得对器官做活检...肺部 肾脏 还有肝
Need to biopsy his actual/organs... lungs,kidneys,liver.
插个针头 他会大出血
We stick another needle/in him,he'll hemorrhage.
那么就按淀粉样变性病来治疗
Unless we start/treatment for amyloidosis.
万一不是淀粉样变性病呢?
Unless it's not amyloidosis.
如果他有感染 放射会害死他
If he has an infection,the/radiation will kill him.
感染的证据呢
Show me evidence of infection.
两小时太短了
We need more than two hours.
有些培养至少得花上一天
Some of these cultures will/take at least a day to grow.
一天后他就死了
He'll be dead in a day.
正如他所预言的
Like he predicted.
不 只需半天 他就会挂
No. He'll be half a day off.
如果我让你们啰嗦个三分钟/再下令按淀粉样变性病治疗...
Would it make you guys feel any better/if I let you argue with me for...
你们会感觉好点吗?
three minutes before I order/you to treat for amyloidosis?
我看也不会 直接治疗吧
No. Just treat for amyloidosis.
不 别去
No. Don'T.
你拿Cuddy来吓唬我?
You're playing the cuddy card?
不然我在这干吗
That's why I'm here.
淀粉样变性病是你想到的
Amyloidosis was your idea.
我错了
I was wrong.
我也是
Yeah,me too.
你一向都很闷
You were never fun.
给我输血
Give me the blood.
我是AB型的
I'm type ab.
给我输吧
Give me the blood.
那些血有问题 所以他奄奄一息
whatever's in there/could be killing him.
什么问题?
In where?
你以为这里的血都被污染了?
How much tainted blood do/you think they keep in here?
那出事的病人该有多少啊...
How many people would/have gotten sick...
得用他脾脏手术时输的那批血 ...
it would have to have been the/first batch,the splenectomy...
症状在那之后出现
that's when the symptoms started.
好 就用那批血
Okay. So transfuse/blood from those donors.
我不会有事
I'll be fine.
就能消除疑点
We move on.
然后按淀粉样变性病来治
Treat for amyloidosis.
来吧
Fill 'er up.
我有新理论
I have a new theory.
你不是固执
You're not stubborn.
你不去检查 是因为你已经知道结果了
You're not getting it checked/'cause you already know the answer.
我在你钱包里发现一张旧照片
I found an old picture in your wallet.
真是你的作风
Of course you did.
我不是偷窥
I wasn't snooping.
我借点钱买午饭
I needed lunch money.
我猜那是你妈妈 但看起来只有32岁
Figure it's your mom,except/she looks about 32 years old.
20多年都没换新照片 唯一原因是
The only reason not to/update a photo in 20-odd years
她和你不来往了
is she's not talking to you,
那让人很好奇...又或者 她死了
which would be/interesting,or she's dead.
也让人好奇
Which would also be interesting.
她死了
She's dead.
克利夫兰也死了 有什么好奇怪/(22届和24届美国总统)
So's grover cleveland.
你这么年轻 妈妈就死了
Pretty young to have a dead mom.
尤其是20年前 那时你才多大
You were even younger 20 years ago.
我上网查了她的讣告
I googled her obituary.
说是她卧病很久/最后死于纽黑文的长老会医院
Said she died at new haven/presbyterian after a long illness.
帕金森病?
Parkinson's?
亨廷顿舞蹈病
Huntington's chorea.
真遗憾
I'm sorry.
这个病例结束了我就走
I'm leaving when this case is over.
你不用走
No,you're not.
你的团队里不需要一个
You don't want a doctor on your team
身体和大脑都逐渐失控的医生
who's slowly losing control/of her body and mind.
亨廷顿不是导致颤抖的唯一原因
Huntington's isn't the only/thing that causes tremors.
你认为只是巧合?
You think it's just a coincidence?
组里只有你喝脱咖啡因咖啡
I think you're the only one/on the team who drinks decaf.
那次你掉落文件之后/我就把你的咖啡换成普通咖啡
I've been switching it out with regular/ever since you dropped that file.
你颤抖是受了咖啡因的刺激
You're trembling 'cause/you're hopped up on caffeine.
弄掉文件那次和我无关
The first file wasn't my fault.
医学上的解释是...
Medical explanation for that is...
人总有失手的时候
people drop things.
我陷入死期将近的恐惧中
I've been walking around/thinking I'm dying...
确实是
you are.
你太残忍了
You don't know that.
如果得了亨廷顿舞蹈病 那是必然的
With huntington's,it's inevitable.
连我自己也不能确定 你又怎么能肯定
No,you don't know,because I don't know.
你怎么不去检查?
How could you not get tested?
母亲遗传给孩子的几率是50%/好像随时会引爆的炸弹
If your mom had it,it's a 50% chance/you're a bomb waiting to explode.
正因为不知道/我才敢去尝试我原本恐惧的事
Not knowing makes me do things/i think I'm scared to do...
参加飞行课 攀爬乞力马扎罗山/还有...做你的下属
take flying lessons,climb/kilimanjaro,work for you.
难道知道了 你就连一样也做不来
'Cause if you knew,you/couldn't do any of those things.
怎么了?
What?
你在冒汗
You're sweating.
发烧了
You're burning up.
House...
你病了
you're sick.
可能是肺炎球菌
could be pneumococcus.
那会引起胸口疼痛以及颈部僵硬
That'd cause chest/pain and the stiff neck.
不是肺炎球菌
It's not pneumococcus.
让我看看你的淋巴结
Let me check your lymph nodes.
我不是病人
I'm not the patient.
身体机能衰竭的那个人才是
Patient is the one whose/body is shutting down.
我这是良性输血反应
I'm having a benign/transfusion reaction.
肺炎球菌会使腋下出现红疹
Pseudomonas would/present as an armpit rash.
把衬衫脱了
Take off your shirt.
你脱我就脱
You first.
House 你得让检查
House,you gotta let us do this.
他不能做活检 否则会出血致死
We can't biopsy him without/bleeding him to death.
想给我做活检 没门
You are not biopsying me.
肚子感觉如何? 有腹泻吗?
How's your stomach? Any diarrhea?
输血量越大 反应越明显
The more transfusions you have,the/greater the chance of you reacting.
我十年中只输过三次
I've had three in a decade.
几小时后就会退烧了
Fever'll be gone in a couple of hours.
有些医生对症状视而不见
I heard somewhere that/doctors ignore symptoms
认为自己百病不侵
because they think they can't get sick.
你让我们给你输血 这样你才...
you told us to give you the/blood so that you wouldn't...
我没病
I am not sick.
发烧就是症状
Fever is a symptom.
病人没有这个症状!
But not of what the patient has!
我的肾功能很正常
My kidneys are working.
其他器官也没有在出血
I'm not bleeding out of every organ.
暂时没有
Yet.
纯属浪费时间
This is a waste of time.
分散了你们的注意力
And it's distracting/you from the actual case.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
房间在旋转
The room is spinning.
你还行吗?
You okay?
不 头晕
No,I'm dizzy.
还有口干
My mouth just went dry.
这症状可能是...
Could be a symptom of any number...
这是麻醉药的症状
it's a symptom of narcotics.
谁给我下了药...
Who spiked my...
你给他下了什么药?
what'd you drug him with?
Amber是蛇蝎女 你却怀疑我
Amber's nickname is cutthroat/bitch,and you're pointing at me.
肾脏取样好了
Got the kidney sample.
只有你稳赚不赔
You're the only one/with nothing to lose.
可能就是你
Could have been you.
你似乎对得不得到工作无所谓
You don't seem to care if/you get this job or not.
是的 我已经在这呆了8星期
Yeah,I've been here for eight weeks
因为我订的"性虐待周刊"到期了
'cause my subscription to/masochism weekly ran out.
你是唯一没要我手下留情的
You're the only one who hasn't asked/me not to put them on the block.
你要么选我 要么不选
You're either gonna/pick me or you're not.
你够公平 会做出正确的决定
You're fair enough to try/to make the right decision,
也够傲慢 我说什么都不能改变你想法
and arrogant enough that nothing/I can say will change your mind.
我不想结束 但是...
I don't want it to be over,but...
我担忧也不能改变什么
unless worrying about it is/gonna make a difference...
我去测试样本
I'm gonna run some stains.
他不会再那么让你讨厌
He'll be less of an ass to you.
病人死了没?
Patient dead yet?
没有
No.
这第一次约会够让人受的
That's a little much for a first date.
跟我约会过 才知道厉害了
Obviously,you've never dated me.
感觉你已经取好了...
Feels like you already got the...
肺和肾的取样...
lung and kidney samples.
现在我要取你的一点肝脏
Now I just need a piece of your liver.
嗨 你也许可以用点麻醉剂...
Hey,you might wanna use/a little lidocaine...
哦 是的 忘了
oh,yeah,I forgot.
稍微有点刺痛
Slight pinch.
你给我下药
You drugged me.
你先给我下的药
去了实验室
Stopped by the lab.
兵变小分队担心要被流放去皮特克恩岛/(喻英国Bounty军舰叛变的故事)
Your mutinous team is starting to/worry about life on pitcairn island.
你的活组织检查全没问题
All your biopsies are clean.
因为我没病
Because there's nothing wrong with me.
Foreman最后同意/进行淀粉样变性病治疗了吗?
Did foreman finally okay/the amyloidosis treatment?
病人定于9点做放射治疗
Patient's scheduled/for irradiation at 9:00.
你差点又把命搭了进去
You risked your life again.
你不能肯定他得了淀粉样变性病
You couldn't be sure he had amyloidosis.
你怎么知道我不肯定
You can't be sure that/I couldn't be sure.
你进行了测试 结果呈阴性
You did one test. It was negative.
没结论
Inconclusive.
然后往体内灌注可能致命的血液
Well,then,by all means flood your/body with possibly lethal blood.
我通常喜欢把致命的血输给Foreman
I usually like to give the/lethal blood to foreman,
但AB血型的就我一个
but I'm the only one who's type AB.
当然 你是AB型
Of course. You're type ab.
全能接收者
Universal recipient.
你从所有人那里获得
You take from everybody.
当然 你是o型血...全能捐赠者
Course,you're type o... universal donor.
难怪要支付三份赡养费
No wonder you're paying three alimonies.
你怎么知道...
How do you know...
我是什么血型?
what blood type I am?
我不知道 不过拿来比喻正合适
I don'T. Just seemed/to fit the metaphor.
不不不
No,no,no,no,no.
你测过我血型吗?
Did you test my blood for something?
为什么你要测我血型?
Why would you test my/blood for something?
我没有
I didn'T.
你一定...告诉过我
You must have...told me what you were.
谁会跟别人聊自己的血型?
Who the hell chats/about their blood type?
你一定测试过我
You had to have tested me.
问别人血型毫无理由
There's no reason to ask/anyone their blood type.
你打算跑出去了吧?
You're about to run/out of here,aren't you?
护士 我能跟病人单独呆会吗?
Nurse,can I have a/moment with my patient?
他要进行放射治疗了
He's due in radiation.
太晚了
It's too late.
他要死了
He's dying.
告诉你了
Told you.
抱歉 我没信你
I'm sorry I doubted you.
把秘密带进坟墓太可惜了
Be a shame if your/secrets died with you.
也许你把窍门记在哪儿了?
Perhaps you've got that/trick written down somewhere?
也许你告诉我 好让我替你记下
Or maybe you wanna tell me,and/I'll write it down for you.
这样...你可以虽死犹生
That way...you can live on.
我要把秘密一起带走
I'm taking it with me.
这样魔力之树可以常青
See,that way,it stays magic.
你全错了
You were wrong about everything.
不存在什么魔力 你也不会死
It was never magic,and you're not dying.
你是什么血型?
What's your blood type?
A型
T-type A.
怎么了?
What?
相信我
Trust me.
揭晓真相那才叫酷
It's way cooler to know.
Finn呢?
where's finn?
我袖子上
Up my sleeve.
他得的不是淀粉样变性病
It's not amyloidosis.
他的血没问题
And his blood's fine.
我们输错了血型
We just gave him the wrong type.
导致弥散性血管内凝血 解释了出血现象
'Caused the D.I.C.,Explains/the bleeding.
和多系统功能衰竭
Multisystem failures.
但是我们验过血
But we tested his blood.
没有验血型
That's because we don't/test blood for type.
验的是抗体
We test for antibodies.
身体根据血型制造抗原和抗体
'Cause your body only makes those antibodies/when you actually have that type of blood.
显然 他的症状不止一项
Apparently,he has one more symptom.
他的身体制造另一种抗原...B抗原/(片中对于血型和抗体的描述有误)
His body's making an/extra antibody...type B.
结合他自有的A抗原 魔法失控了
Combine that with his natural/type a,and presto change-o,
他神奇地变出了AB血型
he magically pulls blood/type ab out of his hat.
你能停下吗?
Would you stop that?
天哪 是的!
God,yes!
自身免疫性疾病/会导致抗体紊乱 但...
autoimmune diseases can make/antibodies go haywire,but still...
这事发生过...
it's happened...
显然又再次发生
and apparently,it's happened again.
我终于有个狼疮病例了
I finally have a case of lupus.
给他输大量盐水
Flush him with saline.
输入4个单位的A型血
Transfuse four units type A.
用类固醇
Start him on steroids.
很快他就可以回去糊弄白痴了
He'll be back hoodwinking/idiots in no time.
博爱 站起来
Big love,rise.
聪明地运用权力 我的君主
Use their power wisely,my lord.
我提名...Amber
I nominate...amber.
蛇蝎女...
Cutthroat bitch...
站起来
rise.
你惊讶吗?
You're surprised?
人人都会选你
You're everyone's pick.
下一个牺牲品
Next victim.
我提名...Kutner
I nominate...kutner.
大家都觉得惊讶 为什么?
Now everyone's surprised. Why?
你说我选择谁 无需解释
You said I don't have/to justify my picks.
不 我说随便你用什么标准
No. I said you could use/whatever criteria you want.
不代表我不想知道
Doesn't mean I don't wanna know.
这是个棘手的病例 他说对了
He was right about/this being a real case.
他说要输液除了错 也对了
He was right about the/botched transfusion.
他还是你的甜心密友
And he's your love nugget.
你没理由选他
You got no reason to pick him.
可别人有理由
But somebody else does.
Kutner是你交换的商品
Kutner's a liability.
他给自己电击 让病人着火
He electrocuted himself,lit/a patient on fire.
迟早他会把整个医院给烧毁
It's only a matter of time/before he burns the hospital down.
你跟Cuddy作了比交易
You made the deal with cuddy.
所以你得到了她的内裤
That's how you got her underwear.
她卖给你内裤 换来她的选择权
She sold it to you for the right/to put her choices on the block.
你说拿到她内裤
You said get her underwear.
我拿到了
I got it.
你的策略很高明
Your scheme was brilliant.
你被解雇了
And you're fired.
是你说要无视规矩的
You're all about breaking the rules.
她的规则 不是我的
Her rules,not mine.
这件事的关键就是跟Cuddy搞破坏
The whole point of this/was to subvert cuddy.
而你成了她同伙 赋予她权力
You became her partner,gave her/power she didn't already have.
让她在我的饼干罐里挑挑拣拣
Let her greedy fingers/into my cookie jar,
虽然没我说得这么不堪
which,sadly,is not/as dirty as it sounds.
感谢你的参与
Thanks for playing.
这到底是什么?
What the hell is this?
似乎是装有/亨廷顿舞蹈症基因测试结果的信封
Looks like an envelope with the results of/the genetic test for huntington's inside.
你看了吗?
Did you look?
我俩一起看结果更有意思
I thought it'd be fun/to find out together.
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
不 你是害怕知道
No. You're afraid to know.
我可能会死 你也一样
I might die. So could you.
你明天可能就被车撞死
You could get hit by a bus tomorrow.
唯一的区别是你今天不必知道
The only difference is you don't/have to know about it today,
为什么我要知道?
so why should I?
我不必知道中奖彩票号码
I don't have to know/the lottery numbers.
可如果有人非要告诉我 我会接受
But if someone offered/them to me,I'd take them.
人一辈子都在寻求答案...
You spend your whole life/looking for answers...
总是以为下一个答案将改变人生
because you think the next/answer will change something,
不再那么悲惨
maybe make you a little less miserable.
可是当疑题一一破灭
And you know that when/you run out of questions,
不仅没有了答案
you don't just run out of answers.
也失去了希望
You run out of hope.
你满意了吗?
You glad you know that?